A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 41597), 1987-1999.
  - State: Health, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Legislative Services, Division of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: State Library, Virginia, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: State Police, Virginia, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - Federal: Agriculture, Dept. of (USDA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Army, Dept. of th, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Navy, Dept. of th, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Energy, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1994 Jan-Apr. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1994 May-Aug. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1994 Sept-Dec. (Box 28)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmosperic Administration (NOAA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Federal: Transportation, Dept. of (USDOT), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: American Red Cross, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Disaster Response Fund, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Emergency Management Program, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Hazard Grant Mitigation Program, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Hazard Mitigation, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Hazardous Material, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Hazardous Material Transportation Act, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: IFLOWS, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: National Governors Association (NGA), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Radiation Advisory Board, 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: Regional Interagency Steering Committee (RISC), 1994. (Box 28)
  - Subject: National Disaster Assistance, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Preparation, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Regional Interagency Steering Committee (RISC) - Donation Management, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: SARA Title III, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue - Urban, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Russian Low Enriched Uranium, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Defueled Reactor Plants, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Foreign, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Navy, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Survivable Crisis Management, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Telecommunications, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Virginia Drought Task Force, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company, 1994. (Box 29)
  - Subject: Virginia Shelter Program, 1994. (Box 29)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Jan. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Feb. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Mar. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Apr. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 May. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 June. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 July. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Aug. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Sept. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Oct. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Nov. (Box 30)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1995 Dec. (Box 30)
  - Program: Campbell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Grants Administration Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Support Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Division, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1995 Jan-Mar. (Box 31)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1995 Apr-June. (Box 31)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1995 July-Sept. (Box 31)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1995 Oct-Dec. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Agriculture, Dept. of (USDA), 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Army, Dept. of the, 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Navy, Dept. of the, 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1995 Jan-Apr. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1995 May-Aug. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1995 Sept-Dec. (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1995. (Box 31)
  - Federal: Transportation, Dept. of (USDOT), 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Conservation and Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Environmental Quality, Dept. of (DEQ), 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Health, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State: Social Services, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 32)
  - State: State Library, Virginia, 1995. (Box 32)
  - State: State Police, Virginia, 1995. (Box 32)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 32)
  - State: Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: American Red Cross, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Central United States Earthquake Consortium (CUSEC), 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Disaster Response Assistance, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Emergency Management Assistance, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Emergency Medical Services Advisory Board, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Hampton Roads Emergency Management Committee, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Hazardous Materials, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Hazardous Materials Transportation Uniform Safety Act (HMTUSA), 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Hazard Grant Mitigation Program, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Mitigation, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Mobile Command Post, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1995 Jan-Apr. (Box 32)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1995 May-Aug. (Box 32)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1995 Sept-Dec. (Box 32)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Radiation Advisory Committee, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Preparedness, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Regional Interagency Steering Committee, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: SARA Title III, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Navy, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Survivable Crisis Management, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Terrorism Response, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Virginia Drought Task Force, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company, 1995. (Box 32)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Jan. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Feb. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Mar. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Apr. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 May. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 June. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 July. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Aug. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Sept. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Oct. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Nov. (Box 33)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1996 Dec. (Box 33)
  - Program: Campbell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Environmental Programs Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Grants Administration Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Support Division, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Branch, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Program: Training Section, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1996 Jan-Mar. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1996 Apr-June. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1996 July-Sept. (Box 34)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Kilgore), 1996 Oct-Dec. (Box 34)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Code Commission, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. o, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: State Library, Virginia, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: State Police, Virginia, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - State: Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Agriculture, Dept. of (USDA), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Army, Dept. of the, 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1996 Jan-Apr. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1996 May-Aug. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1996 Sept-Dec. (Box 34)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Federal: Transportation, Dept. of (USDOT), 1996. (Box 34)
  - Subject: American Red Cross, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Boy Scout Jamboree, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Disaster Response Fund, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Emergency Broadcast System, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Emergency Management, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Fire Suppression Activities, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Floodplain Management, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Floodplain Management and Insurance Program - Dam Safety, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Hampton Roads Emergency Management Committee, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Hazardous Materials training, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Hazard Mitigation, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1996 Jan-Apr. (Box 35)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1996 May-Aug. (Box 35)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1996 Sept-Dec. (Box 35)
  - Subject: National Mitigation Strategy, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: NFPA 1600 Standard, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Old Dominion Emergency Medical Services Alliance, Inc., 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Performance Partnership Agreement (PPA), 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plans, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Regional Interagency Steering Committee, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Regional Response Program, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Spent Fuel, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Telecommunications Services, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1996. (Box 35)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company, 1996. (Box 35)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Jan. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Feb. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Mar. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Apr. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 May. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 June. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 July. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Aug. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Sept. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Oct. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Nov. (Box 36)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1997 Dec. (Box 36)
  - Program: Environmental Program Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Public Information Office, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Support Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Division, 1997. (Box 36)
  - Governor: Allen, George F., 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Chief of Staff - Jay Timmons, 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Administration (Michael E. Thomas), 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of the Commonwealth (Betsy Beamer), 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Commerce and Trade (Robert Skunda), 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Natural Resources (Becky Norton Dunlop), 1994-1997. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Public Safety, 1997 Jan-Mar. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Public Safety, 1997 Apr-June. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Public Safety, 1997 July-Sept. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Secretary of Public Safety, 1997 Oct-Dec. (Box 37)
  - Governor: Virginia Liaison Office, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Other state agencies, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Code Commission, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Health, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: State Library, Virginia, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: State Police, Virginia, 1997. (Box 37)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 37)
  - Federal: Agriculture, Dept. of (USDA), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Army, Dept. of the, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 Jan-Feb. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 Mar-Apr. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 May-June. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 July-Aug. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 Sept-Oct. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1997 Nov-Dec. (Box 38)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Federal: Transportation, Dept. of (USDOT), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: American Red Cross, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Boy Scout Jamboree, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Disaster Response Fund, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Floodplain Management, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Hazardous Materials, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Hazard Mitigation, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Management Information Systems Technical Committee (MIST), 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Mitigation, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: National Warning System, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: Natural Disaster Protection Act, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1997. (Box 38)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1997 Jan-Apr. (Box 39)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1997 May-Aug. (Box 39)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1997 Sept-Dec. (Box 39)
  - Subject: National Governors Association, 1997. (Box 39)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1997. (Box 39)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1997. (Box 39)
  - Subject: Southern States Energy Board (SSEB) - Advisory Committee on Radioactive Materials Transportation, 1997. (Box 39)
  - Subject: Telecommunications Services, 1997. (Box 39)
  - Subject: Virginia Power Company, 1997. (Box 39)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Jan. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Feb. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Mar. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Apr. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 May. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 June. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 July. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Aug. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Sept. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Oct. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Nov. (Box 40)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1998 Dec. (Box 40)
  - Program: Finance Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS) Supervisor, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Management Information Systems Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Preparedness and Mitigation Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Public Information Office, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Recovery and Administrative Services Division, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Branch, 1998. (Box 40)
  - Program: Training Section, 1998. (Box 40)
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 53598), 1995-2013.
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Jan. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Feb. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Mar. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Apr. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 May. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 June. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 July. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Sept. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Oct. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Nov. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2004 Dec. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) binder, 2004. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP), 2004 Mar 24. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP), 2004-2005. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) COOP, 2004-2005. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP), 2004-2005. (Box 1)